Hi, my name is Lanie McCormick.
I'm a fine art photographer in Austin, Texas.
In setting up your dry workstation in your darkroom, you want to have a workbench set away from your wet area.
You are going to house your enlarger here, timer, your safe light and any other printing supplies that you're going to need.
You're also going to house your paper in this area.
You're definitely going to want one of these, your dry station; it's a perfect tool for context sheets.
They're easy to make.
All you need is a piece of glass or Plexiglass and a piece of foam board.
You use these to make your context sheets.
It keeps the negatives flat, inexpensive and very important.